ttiinc.com 2003-06-04

# TTI Inc. - Electronic Components Distributor

**STATEMENT OF PRIVACY**

It's important to TTI Inc. to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. To protect your privacy, ttiinc.com follows five principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection. 

PRINCIPLE 1 -- NOTICE We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before downloading free software, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters or joining a limited-access premium site. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes: To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. To help you quickly find software, services or information on ttiinc.com. To help us create content most relevant to you. To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from TTI Inc.. 

PRINCIPLE 2 - CONSENT If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of ttiinc.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. If you decide to register, you will be able to select the information you want to receive from ttiinc.com by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want ttiinc.com to communicate with you about other offers regarding TTI Inc. products, programs, events, or services by e-mail, postal mail, or telephone, you may visit the ttiinc.com Profile Center, and establish your preferences in the Free Newsletters and Contact Options section. ttiinc.com occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services, using postal mail only. If you do not want to receive these offers, you should uncheck the Contact Options section stating, "TTI Inc. partners can send me postal mail about their services or products." 

PRINCIPLE 3 - ACCESS We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the Profile Center. The Profile Center is akin to a visitor center. There, you can: View and edit personal information you have already given us. Tell us whether you want ttiinc.com to send you marketing information, or whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail. Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products. Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on ttiinc.com, your information stays with you. 

PRINCIPLE 4 - SECURITY ttiinc.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

PRINCIPLE 5 - ENFORCEMENT If for some reason you believe ttiinc.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at webmaster@ttiinc.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line. 

ELECTRONIC PRODUCT REGISTRATION When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we merge your registration information with any information you've already left with us (we call that information your personal profile). If you haven't previously registered with us, we create a personal profile for you from your product registration information. If you ever want to review or update that information, you can visit the Profile Center and edit any of the Personal Information in your profile. If you haven't already registered by giving us your e-mail address and a password, we will ask you to do so. This ensures that only you can access your information. 

CUSTOMER PROFILES As mentioned above, every registered customer has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification number, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile. When you register, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code. This code is uniquely yours. It enables seamless travel across ttiinc.com, allowing you to download free software, order free newsletters, and visit premium sites without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won't have to re-register - just use your e-mail address and password to identify yourself. Be sure to read our privacy FAQ below: 

Q: What is a cookie, and how does a cookie affect my privacy? 

A: Please read our separate q/a about cookies. It should help you understand how cookies help you navigate our site. 

Q: How exactly does registration information help you provide me better content? 

A: Today, the ttiinc.com site is comprised of more than 300,000 Web pages of content. That's equivalent to more than 300 very thick novels. Finding what you need among those pages can be intimidating. But when you tell us about yourself - for example, that you're an IT professional - we can suggest content you might find useful. The better we know you, the more specific information we can suggest. If you want us to, we will also send you product or information updates that help you stay abreast of changes in your industry. 

Q: How can I quit a registration wizard before finishing, and what happens to the information I've already typed in? 

A: If you begin a registration form, then decide you don't want to finish it, just click the cancel button on the bottom of the page. You will be delivered to the entry page of the Profile Center. None of the information entered on the page where you quit the wizard will be saved. However, information entered on previous pages of that wizard, if any, will be saved in our database.
